Jai Hind friends, welcome to a new informative video.
Friends, today in this video we will
talk about loan guarantee for PO program.
We get a lot of queries.
In that query, many people
say that if we are not getting a loan then
how will we go. In this video we
will discuss how you can go into PO program without a
loan
and how you can find a solution for it. So
friends, if you are new to our channel then do like and
subscribe because I bring
updates on banking and finance on this channel.
You will get all the notifications related to jobs on our channel, be it
from government or private banks.
Let's start the video. Friends, a
lot of people have gone through our channel in the PO program and
still a lot of people are going. So we are getting a lot of
concerns. People are
getting a lot of comments that sir, if the loan is
not being given then how will we go, what will happen? So
friends, first of all, it is important to see
that i bank has stopped giving loans in the last 6 months. If you are
not getting a loan, then
you can take a loan from some other bank.
Or if you are not getting a loan then your  You have many other
options because if you see,
after your 4 months of classroom training, when you come, you will start getting a salary of
around Rs. 18200 in your internship,
so at that
time you can arrange money for a few days,
first of all you can arrange money from friends,
family, anywhere,
after this after four to five months
you can settle all the money by taking a personal loan in your name, you
have this
option, you can think about this,
what is the second option, gold loan is a better option,
if you want to go for PO program then
gold loan is a better option,
your gold is kept in your house,
you should keep that gold in the bank,
in the bank, there is also a provision for gold loan in many banks that you take a gold loan, you pay the
interest and after a year you get the money, by
paying it you can get the gold redeemed, so this can also be a better option for you, what will happen in gold loan, that after a year you
can get the gold redeemed, so this can also be a
better option for gold loan,
what will happen in gold loan, that after a year
After this, when you start getting your full salary,
you can get your gold loan released by taking a loan of ₹1 lakh,
this
is also a better option for you or the third option is that if
your parents are employed, then you
can take a personal loan from there, so
you will have to look somewhere or if we look at loans from other banks, then there is a
little concern that
I have received a lot of feedback from many banks
that I apply in other banks
but it is not happening, then
you can look at this option,
I have told you all the three options
because if you see, then your
problem is only for 4 months, if you arrange the money,
after coming from there,
after getting employed in ICICI Bank, ICICI Bank will
give you a loan of ₹3 lakh,
you can settle the entire loan later by taking that money
and this is a job guarantee, there is
nothing to fear in this that you might get
fired after 4 months, many people
also say this, I suggest, people
also say that if you did not get it then there is no job
Then what is the guarantee of your job,
your job is confirmed provided
you do not get caught in any compliance, otherwise your job will
continue forever and your career in a bank like I Bank is
very bright, so
friends,
I have tried to clear the concerns related to loan, so
friends, I hope the video is informative,
please like and share, thank you very
much.